**PRIVACY POLICY**

GENERAL

Your privacy is important to us. This privacy policy is intended to give you confidence in the privacy and security of the personal information we obtain from you whether you are browsing our website or submitting a case inquiry.

COLLECTION OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

When submitting a case inquiry or Live Chat through our website, you you may be asked for personally identifiable information such as your name, address, email address, telephone number. You may also voluntarily provide confidential medical information to us or the company that provides chat services for our website.

By giving us such information, you will need to consent to our using it in the manner described in this policy.

If you would like to opt-out from the disclosure of your personal information to any third party for marketing purposes please contact us at: [\[email protected\]](https://www.necformulahelp.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection), or use this opt-out link: [https://www.linkwindowgold.com/o-kkjm-i33-8478ee1b8ead32c279f5f323b8dbf3a1](https://www.linkwindowgold.com/o-kkjm-i33-8478ee1b8ead32c279f5f323b8dbf3a1) We will return or destroy your personal information within five days of receipt of your withdrawal of consent.

Cookie information, pages you have requested and your IP address may also be recorded by us and/or third parties from your browser as set out in this policy.

USE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

We use personal information to allow us to answer your questions and evaluate your potential case. We do not use it for any other purpose. We do not disclose your information to any person, law firm, or entity for any purpose other than to review your case inquiry. Lawyers, law firms, and their staff not affiliated with this website or agents or employees of Total Injury Help may be asked to review your case to determine if you have a viable claim or lawsuit. Those law firms may contact you directly to determine if you wish to retain them to provide you legal representation for your case. By submitting an online case review inquiry through our Contact Box for live chat, you are consenting to have us forward your submitted information to another law firm for a case review.

DISCLOSURE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

We will not disclose your personal information to any person or entity other than the lawyers, law firms, and legal staff who may evaluate your lawsuit claim.

COOKIES

Cookies are small data files that a website you visit may save on your computer or handheld device that usually includes an anonymous unique identifier. Our Websites and those of our Products may use cookies for user authentication, keeping track of your preferences, promotional campaigns, tracking our audience size and traffic patterns, and in certain other cases. We may include small graphic images in our email messages and newsletters to determine whether the messages were opened and the links were viewed.

SECURITY

All security on our Websites is treated seriously. Where applicable, we undertake security steps, including use of SSL technology, on our back-end systems that store customer account information and to protect data transmissions. However, this is not a guarantee that such data transmissions cannot be accessed, altered or deleted due to firewall or other security software failures.

POLICY CHANGES

Changes in this policy will be posted on our Websites. You are advised to check our Websites regularly to view our most recent privacy policy.
